Some things shouldn't be disturbed.
The Rig is a action, horror, science fiction film directed by Peter Atencio.
In the midst of a tropical storm, the crew of an offshore oil rig must survive
the rampage of a creature after invading its undersea habitat.
Jim Fleming, played by William Forsythe.
Freddy Brewer, played by Stacey Hinnen.
Carey Fleming, played by Serah D'Laine.
Andrew, played by Marcus T. Paulk.
Rodriguez, played by Carmen Gloria Pérez.
Colin Brewer / The Creature, played by Dan Benson.
On April 20, 2010, an explosion and fire occurred on the Deepwater Horizon semi-submersible mobile offshore drilling unit, which was owned and
operated by Transocean and drilling for BP in the Macondo Prospect oil field about 40 miles (64 km) southeast off the Louisiana coast.
The explosion and subsequent fire resulted in the sinking of the Deepwater
Horizon and the deaths of 11 workers; 17 others were injured.
The same blowout that caused the explosion also caused an oil well fire and a massive offshore oil spill in the Gulf of Mexico,
considered the largest accidental marine oil spill of all time, and the largest environmental disaster in United States history.
The film explores themes of sea, monster, oil rig .
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.